Good night.
Thanks for watching.
I've been rolling around on my bike lately, so I hit it too.
What do you want me to do?
Wait a minute.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Hello. - Hello.
Hi. Hi.
What?
Turn around.
Yeah?
Thank you for coming.
Slow down.
Here's the family egg and this one.
This one here... you take it for the tama.
That's how we do it.
Thank you for watching.
What is rhythm?
What rhythm?
Are you mad?
Angry?
Oh, there we go. There we go. There we go.
Good, good, good, good.
Good, good, good, good, good, good, good.
Let me get lost for a second.
Let me give you a little beach rub, then, shall I?
My fingernails quit clawing.
He's got quit claws, too.
I'll show you. They're quitting.
You don't know so much, do you?
How can you be so careful?
Wait a minute.
You're so cute!
You're cute.
That was a commercial for social services.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What? Cute!
Why are you so cute!
You're so cute!
You're cute!
No, you're cute today.
See you later.
I'm getting better. I'm getting better.
Oh, good.
That's good. That's good.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha
No way.
Good night.
Good night
No, I mean... Hana-chan...
Here's a change.
The grandkids are back.
It was fun.
I think he stayed with us for about a week.
That's a long time.
I'm gonna miss you.
Oh, by the way, newlyweds...
I see you're here again today.
Again.
Did you stay the night?
It's fun.
Wait a minute.
I knew it.
I looked at my grandson for the camera and said, "Okay.
It's okay.
It's just too different from nature.
Oh, man.
This is too good.
Delicious.
These are raw photos, right?
LOL!
What's his face?
His face.
He's 85 years old.
Laughter
Laughter.
Yes, thank you very much.
Are you 79 years old?
Seventy-nine years old.
Laughter
Laughter.
laughter
Come a little bit forward.
A little bit more, let's go around there.
Sis.
Your voice in our house
Sis
Sis.
I saw it in your face!
Oh, no, no, no, no.
I didn't see it.
Good morning.
Actress.
Let's play baseball.
Come on, fall on your belly.
Okay, straight up.
Thank you very much.
You're the same height as me.
The same.
I don't know what that means the most.
Thank you for watching.
Oh, that's nice.
That's nice.
That's important.
Excuse me.
Kanka-chan.
Babies have long legs.
Long legs!
What kind of toy is this?
It's a baby's
I'm borrowing it.
That's how we play with sound
Maybe, yeah, they play with sound.
That kind of thing.
I'm kind of enjoying this.
Cool.
That's all I can think of.
Pause.
Oh, that's good.
That's good.
It's good.
Good.
Really.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
You have the best eyes in the world, Grandma.
Your head is falling off.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
Please, please, please.
Uh-oh.
I'm using Grandpa's.
Grandpa uses it.
Like in front of his face.
Mm-hmm.
Music
music
I tell my dog I hate him.
I used to be a mad dog.
Now he's turning into my grandma.
Go figure.
That's a strange thing to say, granny.
Please be stern with me.
Strictly.
Auntie, give me the whiskers quickly.
Don't stop.
Give me the bites quickly.
Give me some chisel, quick.
Did you start playing baseball today?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Thank you for watching.
My oldest son, you'll only be able to see the back of my head.
My eldest son will be mad at me all the time now.
Just my eldest son. This is a camera.
He's the type of guy who'll get it.
This guy's been great earlier.
That's great. That's great.
He's been great.
I was told not to talk earlier.
Well, I did.
Which sense does that come in? I'm going to talk.
I'm sorry to bother you, but this topic...
I'm going to rap to Ammont.
I'd like to talk about you and Aya.
Just a moment.
My
Isn't Lo cool?
Lo is cool, right?
Lo is cool!
Lo is cool?
Why are you saying that?
I have to say it twice.
Since Nachi said it.
One for each.
That's terrible.
I'm sorry.
I don't know what kind of thing made me sick.
Together.
Oh, shit.
Oh, no.
We're brothers and we're in love.
Look, I'm not in love with anyone.
I won't do it again.
That's a great sound.
I'm not gonna do it again.
Thank you very much for your time.
Thank you very much for your hard work
That's too much work
Thank you for your hard work
There.
Thank you for your hard work.
Hello. - Hello.
Good afternoon, gentlemen.
This one will be...
This one is
This way please.
I'm coming.
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Next time, I'm not so sure.
Bus.
What's wrong with you?
Numb.
Ha-ha-ha
I'm in Tennoji.
This is the Tennoji house.
Fresh photo shoot of the Tennoji house
Daily life edition
Thank you for your hard work
Thank you for watching
I'm glad my grandson annoyed you.
85 years old
No, she's not.
How old is Chie?
No, no, no.
Seventy-nine.
That's good.
How old is Kou?
He turned five.
You started playing baseball!
You got him to watch you.
You bought it.
That's great.
You did it?
You did?
You did it.
Did you do it?
This...
Oh!
Yes!
Yes.
There it is.
Is everyone finished today with this?
Yes, sir.
I'm going to change in the middle of the day.
Thank you for your hard work.